CHI ZHANG

zchangcoding@gmail.com **Q** Edmonton **in** https://www.linkedin.com/in/chi-zhang-4a145386/ **Q** warlocksa

SUMMARY

I can work both front-end and back-end work. Not only feature writing, but also database work or webpage design are good for me. And I think, the best skill I have got is searching the solution by internet, even some works are difficult to me, I can try to find help online. In addition, previous work experience I worked in multi-culture work environment that I was used to work with others. And work did not means that my study-life is end, I will keep study the new tech languages and frameworks to prepare to face more challenges in the future.

SKILLS

IT LANGUAGES: JavaScript, Ruby, HTML, CSS, SQL

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES: NodeJS, React, Express, EJS, jQuery, Rails, Ajax, Axios

SYSTEMS & DATABASES: PostgreSQL, Git

TESTING: Jest, Storybook, Cypress LANGUAGES: English, Chinese

PROJECTS

May 2022 Auto Deal

Pair-work project about tinder like auto trade website. Most of my duties is front-work. Tech Stack: React, express, Node.js, MongoDB

Apr. 2022 Interview-scheduler

React based project to create meetings for students to connect with mentors in real-time.

Tech Stack: React, Js, Axios, Storybook, Jest, Cypress.

LHL_food Apr. 2022

Pair-work project about online food order website and send the sms to both restaurant and customers.

Tech Stack: Js, Ejs, Sass, Jquery, Ajax, Sql, Twilio.

Mar. 2022 Tweeter

Single page project that user can post message and saw others` posts. Tech Stack: Node.js, html, css, Ajax.

Feb. 2022 Tinyapp

A full stack web app built with Node and Express that allows users to shorten long URLs. Tech Stack: node.js, express, ejs.

EMPLOYMENT

Nov. 2019 - Mar. 2020 Paradies Lagardere NA, sales associate, Edmonton

May 2018 - Mar. 2019 Holiday Inn Express & Suites Halifax - Bedford, houseperson, Halifax

May 2014 - Dec. 2017 Fresh Happy Healthy Sushi Restaurant, cook, Halifax

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Lab Web Development Bootcamp Mar. 2022 - May 2022

Diploma Web Development 2022

Mount Saint Vincent University Sept. 2012 - Apr. 2015

Bachelor Tourism and Hospitality Management 2015

Fujian Agriculture and Forest University Sept. 2010 - Apr. 2015

Bachelor Agriculture Resource and Environment 2015